<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Anqi Li Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Anqi's portfolio.]]></description><link>https://anqi-uxr.github.io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 18:47:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[MetaCX: Transforming Suppliers & Buyers Collaboration]]></title><description><![CDATA[Research Associate @ MetaCX]]></description><link>https:/anqi-uxr.github.io/blog/metacx/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/anqi-uxr.github.io/blog/metacx/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;More Details Coming soon…&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Navigating ambiguous problem space in B2B SaaS startup. I am defining user problems to solve through the creation of personas and informing product roadmap through creative research methods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Keywords&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;User Persona, Product Management, User Stories, User Interviews&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[IoT for Agriculture: Remote Beehive Monitoring]]></title><description><![CDATA[Foudational Research for a Student Start-up]]></description><link>https:/anqi-uxr.github.io/blog/hivetec/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/anqi-uxr.github.io/blog/hivetec/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;Project Summary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HiveTec is an early-stage start-up focusing on using technology as a solution to agricultural problems. HiveTec is developing an IoT-based remote monitoring tool for beehives to combat high honeybee colony loss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the primary UX researcher, I conducted a two-month foundational research project to understand U.S. beekeepers’ working processes, challenges, and needs with regards to monitoring beehives and keep bees healthy. As a result, I defined product features for the first-generation MVP by leveraging insights from in-depth interviews and an online survey with hobbyist beekeepers across the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tenzing: Documenting Contributions in Academic Research]]></title><description><![CDATA[User Research Intern @ ChaiOne, Inc.]]></description><link>https:/anqi-uxr.github.io/blog/tenzing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/anqi-uxr.github.io/blog/tenzing/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;Project Summary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During my part-time internship as a User Researcher at ChaiOne, Inc. in fall 2020, I led a client project for Tenzing, a web-app for academic researchers from end-to end including research planning, execution and delivering insights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project was divided into two parts. For the present case study, I would like to focus on the evaluative research of this project, in which I evaluated usability of the web-app, delivered impactful insights, and worked with designer to deliver design solutions for the client.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>